(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
答えはいつも私の胸に...
The answer is always in my heart...
冒険でしょでしょ？
It's an Adventure, Right? Right?
何でだろう 花束を選んだ私です
I wonder why I'm the one who chose a bouquet of flowers
もっと回らない 運命さながら決められたけど
Though it's like a fate that's been decided, unable to turn more
I believe
真似だけじゃつまらないのよ You be right
Just mimicking is boring, you be right
感じるまま 感じることだけを するよ
I'll do exactly what I feel as I feel it
冒険でしょ？でしょ？ 本当が嘘に変わる世界で
It's an adventure, right? Right? In a world where truth turns to lies
夢があるから 強くなるのよ 誰のためじゃない
Having a dream makes me strong, it's not for anyone else's sake
一緒に来てください どこまでも自由な
Please come along with me, to wherever we can be free
私を見てよね 明日過去になった今日の今が奇跡
Keep your eyes on me, today will be the past tomorrow, this moment is a miracle
I believe you
戻れない どこまで行かなきゃ つまんない
I can't go back, unless I keep going it's boring
さあ教えて 秘めてる願いを 鏡に投げた
Now tell me, I threw my hidden wishes at the mirror
My delight
体ごと受け止めたら Your my bright
If I accept it with my whole body, you're my bright
驚かせて 驚いて笑顔に...
Surprise me, be surprised, and turn into a smile...
になろう
Let's become
始まりでしょ でしょ？ 綺麗が闇を
It's a beginning, right? Like how beauty
照らすみたいに
shines through the darkness
私の力 あなたの未来
I want my strength and your future
どっちも照らしたいの
to both be illuminated
現実に揺れる 繊細な心が
My delicate heart, swaying in reality
傷つくのは嫌 思いまして
I don't want it to get hurt, I've always thought
いつもいつも胸の奥に
deep within my chest
答えが
the answer is...
普通じゃないのが 当然なら
If it's only natural that things aren't normal
答える私は 何かできる？
In response, what can I do?
普通でも普通じゃなくて
Even if it's normal, or not normal
感じるまま感じる事だけを するよ
I'll just do whatever I feel like doing
冒険でしょ でしょ？ ホントが嘘に変わる世界で
It's an adventure, right? In a world where truth turns to lies
夢があるから 強くなるのよ 誰のためじゃない
Having dreams makes me stronger, and it's not for anyone else's sake
始まりでしょ でしょ？ 始まりなんでしょ？
It's a beginning, right? This is the start, isn't it?
綺麗が闇を 照らすみたいに
Like how beauty shines through the darkness
私とあなた 冒険の途中
You and I are in the middle of an adventure
一緒に進んでく
Let's move forward together
どこまでも自由に
To wherever we want, freely
現実を超えて
Surpassing reality
明日が過去になった 今が奇跡
The present, where tomorrow has become the past, is a miracle
確かな 未来を
A certain future
つかもう 未来を
Let's grab hold of it, the future
未来を I believe you
The future, I believe you
Ih, yang barusan bagus banget deh!
I think that was our best one yet!
Hihi, iya dong, kompak banget kita. Ha ha!
Yeah! We synced better this time! Ha ha!
Hah... akhirnya bisa juga.
Took awhile to actually get it down though...
Badan udah mau copot nih.
My body feels like it's going to fall apart.
Hehe, tapi jangan encok dulu.
Don't fall over now!
Baru tiga kali kita latihan nih.
This is only what, our 3rd time practicing?
Ya gimana ya...
I know it is~
kaki udah keburu ngendoy bestie.
But I think I need the sewing kit on me, my legs feel loose.
Hah, alat jahit dong.
Give me the sewing kit.
Bentar, emang kamu bisa jadi zombie kayak gini gimana sih ceritanya?
So... how did you get reincarnated anyways?
Heueuh juga ya. Gimana ya?
That's actually a good question... how indeed?
Aku gak pernah kepikiran.
I never really thought about it.
Taunya cuman tiba-tiba kebangun dari kubur terus...
I just suddenly rose from the dead and...
aku jalanin aja.
went on with whatever...
Eh? Jadi selama ini tuh kamu gak tahu gitu
So you're telling me that you don't even know how?
kenapa atau gimananya gitu?
Or why, even?
Ho'oh.
To be honest, yeah.
Oh... gitu kah.
I see...
Ya tapi kalau gitu kenapa gak sekarang aja gitu
Well, you have right now.
mumpung hari ini kan lumayan ada waktu nih.
So why don't you try to look into it just a bit?
Kamu coba gali itu asal-usul kamu tuh.
Try to investigate your origins.
Eh? Tapi kita kan lagi latihan?
Huh? But we're in the middle of dance practice-
Alah, latihan doang bisa lain hari lah, gak apa-apa, gak apa-apa.
We can just practice another day! Don't worry too much~
Bestie...
I love you so so so much!
Tapi aku traktirin ya!
I promise I'll treat you!
Wih, iya jelas lah harus.
Haha! You better!
Dah gih pergi pergi.
Now get out of here!
Nanti kalau udah balik jangan lupa cerita banyak ya.
You better bring me a good story out of it!
Hehe! Oke!
Hehe! I will!
あのね
You know
私 実は気付いてるの
Actually, I've already noticed
ほら 君が言ったこと
Look, the thing that you said
あまり
Not
考えたいと思えなくて
really wanting to think about it
忘れてたんだけど
I'd ended up forgetting it
盲目的で
Blindly,
動道的で
automatically,
妄想的に 生きて
delusionally living.
衝動的な
Impulsive,
焦燥的な
impatient,
消極的なままじゃ 駄目だったんだ
being passive wasn't going to work.
きっと人生最後の日、お前を想うのだろう。
I'll surely think of you on the very last day of my life.
全部全部言い足りなくて惜しいけど。
It's a shame that I haven't said it all.
ああ、いつか人生最後の日、君がいないことを。
Ah, that one day, on the last day of my life, you won't be here.
もっと もっと もっと...
More, more, more...
もっとちゃんと、言って。
Say it properly.
あのね、空が青いのってどうやって伝えればいいんだろうね。
You know, how should I describe that the sky is blue?
夜の雲が高いのってどうすれば君もわかるんだろう。
How do I make you understand that the night clouds are high?
言って。
Say it.
あのね、私、実はわかっているの。もう君が行ったこと。
You know, I actually know... that you've already gone.
あのね、わからずやって言うんだろうね。忘れたいんだけど。
You know, you'd call it being stubborn. I want to forget, though.
もっとちゃんと言ってよ。忘れないようメモにしてよ。
Tell me more properly. Write a note so I won't forget.
明日十時にホームで待ち合わせとかしよう。
Let's meet at the platform at 10:00 AM tomorrow.
牡丹は散っても花だ。夏が去っても追憶は切な。
Peonies are still flowers even when they fall. Even after summer passes, memories are painful.
口に出して。
Say it out loud.
声に出して。
Say it with your voice.
君が言って。
You say it.
そして人生最後の日、君が見えるのなら。
And on the last day of my life, if I can see you...
きっと人生最後の日も愛を歌うのだろう。
I'll surely sing about love on the last day of my life too.
全部全部無駄じゃなかったって言うから。
Because I'll say that none of it was in vain.
ああ、いつか人生最後の日、君がいないことがまだ信じられないけど。
Ah, that one day, on the last day of my life, I still won't believe you're gone.
もっと もっと もっと もっと...
More, more, more, more...
ちゃんと言って。
Say it properly.
Makasih udah bantuin kita bersihin panggung ya Ollie!
Thanks for helping us set up the stage Ollie!
Iya! Tadi kabelnya kusut semua, untung Senpai bantu benerin.
Yeah! We kinda had troubles with the cables, good thing you helped us untangle them!
Hehehe no problem. Malah aku yang seneng lho bisa ketemu sama kalian di sini.
Hehe! No problem. If anything, I'm really happy I got to catch you guys here!
Aku sedikit mau curhat soalnya.
I actually have something in my head recently...
Hm? Ada apa ada apa?
Oh? What's up?
Akhir-akhir ini aku lagi kepikiran, kenapa ya aku jadi zombie?
Lately I've been wondering...
Buat apa gitu lho.
what the reason of my zombie becoming was.
Kalau menurut kalian, aku kenapa jadi zombie?
Why do you guys think I turned into a zombie?
Ooh lagi cari jati diri ya?
Oh you're searching for your identity.
Hmm kalau menurut aku sih, kayaknya masih ada harapan dan hal-hal yang sebenarnya masih pengen kamu capai.
Well, I think there are a lot hopes and things that you want to pursue.
Harapan itu saking kuatnya sampai bikin kamu bangkit lagi jadi zombie.
Because of your strong will and hope, you got reanimated and turned into a zombie.
Ooooh bisa jadi!
That sounds close!
Kalau menurut Zeta?
What do you think is the reason, Zeta?
Kalau menurut aku sih, itu senpai sebenarnya masih pengen bikin memori lebih banyak lagi makanya hidup lagi. Tapi nggak tau deh.
Hmm I think your body just wants to make more happy memories! Maybe!
Hmm menarik! Makasih ya inputnya!
I see! Thanks so much for the input guys!
Mungkin itu jawabannya.
I think those are pretty spot on reasons!
Sama-sama. Moga-moga kamu dapat pencerahan ya!
No problem! Hope you get to find your reason soon!
Semangat Senpai!
Good luck senpai!
Makasih!
Thank you!
わかってる、ほしいんでしょ。
I know, you want it, right?
艶やかなこの唇。
These glossy lips.
柔な男たち惹きよせる、息を呑むほど。
Luring in weak men, to the point they're breathless.
わかってる ほしいんでしょ
I know you want it
艶めいた この身体
This glamorous body
冷めた街 独り歩けば
Walking alone in the cold city
みだらな視線が 絡みつく
Lustful gazes cling to me
ねぇ 何を期待してるの
Hey, what are you expecting?
それじゃなくて まっすぐがいいの
Not that, I want it straight
大人の恋に 焦がれて
Longing for an adult love
見た目よりも残る あどけない
Innocence remains more than looks
心だけが 先走る
Only my heart runs ahead
青い蕾のまま オトナブルー
As a green bud, Otona Blue
わかってる ほしいんでしょ
I know you want it
刺激する 私のすべて
Stimulating my everything
冷めた瞳 まるで魅了する
Cold eyes as if captivating
罪深き花になる あまりにも
Becoming a sinful flower, so much so
優しいだけの 言葉じゃなくて
Not just kind words
心で 繋がりたくて
I want to connect with my heart
ありきたりな メイクじゃ隠せない
Common makeup can't hide it
憧れだけじゃ 夢をみる
Only longing makes me dream
貴方の前では またオトナブルー
Before you, I'm Otona Blue again
それじゃなくて まっすぐがいいの
Not that, I want it straight
大人の恋に 焦がれて
Longing for an adult love
見た目よりも残る あどけない
Innocence remains more than looks
気持ちだけが 空回り
Only my feelings spin in vain
私を みつめて
Look at me
優しいだけの 言葉じゃなくて
Not just kind words
心で 繋がりたくて
I want to connect with my heart
ありきたりな メイクじゃ隠せない
Common makeup can't hide it
憧れだけじゃ 夢をみる
Only longing makes me dream
学びの恋路を 追いかけて
Chasing after the path of love
追いかけて
Chasing after
またオトナ
Otona again
ブルー
Blue
Guuh! Huph! Grrr...! やばいめっちゃ疲れた！
Guuh! Huph! Grrr...! Damn, I'm so tired!
やだーまた負けちゃった！
Nooo I lost again!
Wow talk about skill issue...
Ini mah bukan skill issue!
This is not about skill issue!
Kaela-nya aja yang terlalu OP.
Or maybe Kaela is just too good at this...
Hehe, you'll get the hang of it senpai^^
先輩も練習すればできるさ〜
If you practice a bit you'll get good too!
そういえば、先ほど聞きたいことがあって探してたんじゃなかったっけ？
Oh yeah, didn't you have something you wanted to talk to us about?
あ！
Oh!
そうそう！夢中になりすぎて忘れちゃった！
Right! I got so reeled into the game that I forgot!
Aku nyari kalian soalnya ada yang pengen aku konsulin, pengen nanya kalian.
There's something that I'm curious about and I wanted to ask you guys.
Wuih, konsul apa tuh?
Ask us?
Konsul restoran?
Are you taking us to dinner?
Aku tahu banyak lho yang enak.
I know the place!
Neee... bukan...
Nooo...
Aku tuh... lagi krisis identitas. Atau lebih tepatnya lagi krisis eksistensial.
I'm kind of in the middle of an existential crisis, literally...
Aku lagi heran gitu lho, kok bisa ya aku hidup kembali sebagai zombie?
Trying to figure out why I was resurrected as a zombie in the first place...
Dipikir-pikir... iya juga ya.
Come to think about it...
Kita nggak pernah tahu kenapa.
yeah we never really knew why...
Iya... kira-kira kalian ada ide nggak kenapa?
Yeah... So any guesses?
Hmm, sebenarnya kalau menurut aku, senpai bosen aja kali tiduran mulu di kuburan.
Maybe your body is just bored of being buried?
Jadi pengen bangun. Iya nggak sih? Bingung juga.
I don't know though...
Nah, aku kira wong iki duwe dendam.
I think she holds a grudge
Dadi dheweke durung tenang afterlife-ne.
So she can't feel peace in her afterlife
Hee... bisa juga. Aku nggak pernah kepikiran sampai sana sih.
Huh, never really saw it that way
Kalau Moona-senpai bagaimana?
What about you Moona-senpai, what do you think?
Aku? Hmm...
Me? Hmm...
Mungkin sebelum mati kamu keminum sesuatu?
Maybe you drank something that prevented you from death?
Atau mungkin... kedigigit sesuatu?
Or maybe got bitten by a mysterious creature?
Ya... tapi alasan apapun itu... kamu tetap Ollie kita kok.
Whatever the reason may be... you're still our Ollie so I hope you know that
Kecuali kalau ternyata senpai itu sebenarnya-
Unless you turn out to be a-
Maksudnya Kobo itu, senpai itu mau bentuknya kayak gimana pun juga tetap teman kita.
What she means to say is that... You'll still be our friend senpai
Oh... makasih guys.
Aww... thanks guys
Yo'i!
Yeah!
Kalau gitu aku mau coba tanya-tanya orang lagi ya.
Well I'm going to ask around a bit more!
Semangat latihannya!
Good luck with practice!
Dadah senpai!
See you!
Moga ketemu ya lore-nya!
Good luck with your lore finding!
サンドリヨン
Cendrillon
朝まで踊る 夢だけ見せて
Dance until morning, let me just dream
時計の鐘が 鳴るまで
Until the clock bell rings
曖昧な指 誘う階段
An ambiguous finger beckons from the stairs
三段飛ばしに 跳ねていく
Leaping up three steps at a time
馬車の中で 震えてた
Shivering inside the carriage
惨めな古着
In those miserable old clothes
めぐりめぐれ 夜の舞踏会
Turn and turn, the night's ball
見知らぬ顔 探す 囁く
Searching for an unfamiliar face, whispering...
あの声が
That voice...
握りしめた 刃 突き立て
Brandishing the blade I've gripped tightly
全てを奪えと
“Take everything,” it says
孤児集う城 笑み仮面に
In the castle where orphans gather, upon a smiling mask...
描いて
I draw...
偽りの 慈しみさえ
Even false compassion...
羽で包む セラフ
Is wrapped in wings by a seraph
灰の中で 赤く 溶けて混じる
Melting and mixing red within the ashes
ガラスの靴
A glass slipper
今更帰る 震えているの
You're going home now? You're trembling...
あなたが目をやる 時計
The clock you glance at...
靴脱ぎ踊る スロープ抜けて
Taking off my shoes and dancing, passing the slope
喉まで伸びる 指の先で
With a fingertip reaching up to your throat
すくう雫 口づけて
Kissing the teardrops I scoop up
走る衝動 背骨抜けていく
A rushing impulse surges through my spine
刹那
In an instant
鐘は鳴らさないで
Don't let the bell ring
あなたに跪き
Kneeling before you
「まだだめ」と 叫んだ右手が
My right hand that shouted “Not yet!”
突き刺す サヨナラ
Pierces through a goodbye
消せない香水を 独り纏い
Alone, wearing an indelible perfume
纏わせ
And making you wear it
強い瞳に 僕の横顔
Pressing my profile into your strong eyes
叩き込んで 眠る
Before I sleep
今も耳に あなたの吐息が
Even now, your breath still pierces my ears
突き刺さるの
It's piercing me
遠い夢
A distant dream
ステンドグラス越し 光る月が
The moon shining through the stained glass
君に被せた
Placed upon you...
ベール
A veil
ドレス膝で裂いて
Ripping the dress at the knees
ティアラは投げ捨てて
Throwing away the tiara
見つめあう 瞳と瞳が
Gazing into each other's eyes
火花を放つ
Sending off sparks
孤独な魂が 炎を上げ
Lonely souls burst into flame
惹かれあう
Drawn to one another
その涙 救えないのなら
If those tears cannot be saved
全て独り遊び
It's all just playing alone
時よ止まれ今は
Time, stop now
あなたに酔いしれて
Intoxicated by you
揺れる鼓動 ひとつひとつを
Every single swaying heartbeat
刻みつけていたい
I want to engrave them all
踏みとどまれ 熱く
Hold your ground, hotly...
打ちつける 高鳴りに
Against the pounding throbs
これ以上は 動けないよ
I can't move any further
まるで お伽話
Just like a fairy tale
...zZzz...zZzz...
んん...？
Hmm...?
な...
Wha...
っ！？
!?
みやび先輩！？みやび先輩！？
Miyabi-senpai!? Miyabi-senpai!?
あ、目が覚めたんだね。
Oh, you're awake.
おはよう。
Good morning.
みやび先輩！？
Miyabi-senpai!?
ここで何してるんですか！？
What are you doing here!?
今日は僕もスタジオでのダンスリハーサルがあるんだ。
Well, I have dance practice in the studio today too.
歩いてたら、道端で寝ているオリーを見つけて。
And then I found you sleeping here in the wayside.
うわー！マジですか！？
Gaah! Seriously!?
寝顔をみやび先輩に見られたのでは！？
I showed my sleeping face to Miyabi-senpai!!
オリーは何でここで寝ていたの？
And what about you? Why were you sleeping here?
あ、うー...
Oh, uh...
話は長くなるけど...
It's kind of a long story...
最近、自分の存在の理由が気になって...
I've been thinking about my origins... You know, the reason why I became a zombie...
あ、オリーの実家がラーメン屋に変わったから起きたんじゃないの？
Isn't it because you sensed that your house turned into a ramen shop? Or so I heard.
違うよ！それはたまたま起きた時にラーメン屋だった！
That was actually a coincidence! I happen to wake up and it already was a ramen shop...
それでね...
And you know?
自分の存在について考え始めて...
The more I think about my existence...
自分の運命まで考えちゃって...
The more I think about fate...
なぜ運命がオリーを起こしたんだろう？
Why did it make me live I wonder?
死んだ後に未練でもあるのかなあ？
Why is my grave not the end of my chapter? Can't help it...
そういうことがあったんだ。
I see, so you've been having those thoughts...
大変だね。
It must be hard for you to think about.
でもたまに考えずにそのままにしておいたほうがいいこともあるのって知ってる？
But you know, sometimes there are things that are best left as is...
だから深く考えないで、そのうち答えが出てくるからさ。
I don't think you need to ponder too much about it, surely the answer will come to you on it's own...
そうだね。その通りだね！
You know what... You're right senpai!
焦る必要がないし...
I shouldn't rush too much...
いつかきっと答えが出てくるはず！
Surely I'll find out sooner or later!
役に立ってよかった。
I'm glad I got to help you...
じゃ、リハがあるから先に行ってくるね。
Anyways, I have dance practice so I better take my leave now.
うん！先輩本当にありがとう！
I will! Thank you so much senpai!
元気でね、オリー！
Take care, Ollie!
先輩の言った通りだ。
He's right...
考えすぎなくていい。
I shouldn't think about it too much...
必ず答えが出てくる。
I should just take my time...
Pada akhirnya, bukannya dapet jawaban, malah ngegabut ke mana-mana.
In the end, I just wasted my day looking for an answer that I don't even know exists.
Iofie-senpai sampai aku tinggalin lagi.
I feel bad for bailing on dance practice with Iofie-senpai...
Jadi gak enak aku.
I gotta apologize later...
Jawabannya bakal dateng sendiri... huh.
The answer will come to me sooner or later, huh.
Iya, moga-moga jawabannya gak ngaret datengnya, keburu meninggal lagi aku.
I hope I won't have to wait too long that I get revived a second time.
Andai ada petunjuk sedikit aja.
If only there was some sort of clue.
Eh?
Huh?
Itu... bunga?
Is that a flower?
Kok tumbuhnya di pinggir jalan sih? Aneh.
What's it doing growing at a busy street like this? How weird.
Ini tuh bukan tempat kamu bunga kecil.
This isn't your place little daisy.
Kamu seharusnya tumbuh di tempat lain.
You belong somewhere else where...
Kalo tumbuhnya di sini, yang ada kamu layu.
If you were to stay, then you'll only wilt.
Barusan... apa yang terjadi?
W-What... Just... Happened...?
Bunganya... mekar.
It... Bloomed.
Apa-apaan...
What in the world...
Yang barusan itu... aku?
Did... I do that...?
Jadi... inikah?
...Is this it...?
Trust me, I'll be back in the days...
アダムとイブはどんな気持ちで手に取ったんだ？
With what feelings did Adam and Eve take it in their hands?
青くて苦くて僕は齧って残りは全部捨てたんだ
Green and bitter, I took a bite and threw all the rest away
だって理解できないから 身勝手許されないから
Because I can't understand it, because selfishness isn't forgiven
全部燃やし尽くしていつか笑える日まで Back in the days
Burning it all to the ground, until the day I can laugh, back in the days
産まれ落ちた生命 惑星呪い尽くした所為で
Life that was born into this world, due to the planet being cursed
焼け野原に見えてんだ？かける言葉も見つかりやしないや
Does it look like a burnt field to you? I can't even find any words to say
星が砂に変わってしまったんじゃない
The stars didn't turn into sand
僕の心が砂でできていたんだ
My heart was made of sand
誰もが置き去りにした世界で
In a world that everyone left behind
始まりの歌を歌い続ける もうわかってたんだ
Continuing to sing the song of beginning, I already knew
ひどくしゃがれた声を上げれば
If I raise my voice, so terribly hoarse
また君に会える気がした ねえ、聴こえているんでしょう？
I felt like I could meet you again, hey, you can hear me, right?
Trust me, I'll be back in the days...
僕らは魔法に期待しながら 魔法使いを嫌っていた
While expecting magic, we hated the wizard
都合のいい世界だけを望んで生きている
Living while only wishing for a convenient world
矛盾まみれの人生論と歩いてきた四半世紀
A quarter-century walked with a life philosophy full of contradictions
掛け違えたボタンも笑える日が来るなら
If the day comes when I can laugh at the mismatched buttons
誰もが置き去りにした世界で
In a world that everyone left behind
始まりの歌を歌い続ける もうわかってたんだ
Continuing to sing the song of beginning, I already knew
ひどくしゃがれた声を上げれば
If I raise my voice, so terribly hoarse
また君に会える気がした ねえ、聴こえているんでしょう？
I felt like I could meet you again, hey, you can hear me, right?
Trust me, I'll be back in the days...
足元に転がった赤い果実
The red fruit that rolled at my feet
誰を恨んだりしたいわけじゃない
It's not that I want to resent anyone
...分かってたんだ
...I knew it all along
誰もが置き去りにした世界で
In a world that everyone left behind
はじまりの歌を歌い続ける
I keep singing the song of beginnings
もう気づいてたんだ
I already realized it
ひどく嗄れた声はきっと
This terribly hoarse voice will surely
まだ見ぬ君に届いている
Reach you, whom I've yet to see
ねえ聴こえてるでしょう？
Hey, you can hear it, right?
鏡の中の自分に
To the self inside the mirror
巡り巡る今日を
The recurring today
刻んでいく音を
The sound that carves it
はじめて出会ったんだ
I met it for the first time
鏡の中の自分に
The self inside the mirror
巡り巡る今日を
The recurring today
刻んでいく音を
The sound that carves it
Jadi, begitu!
Now I see!
Ini kah alasan aku hidup kembali?
So this was why I was brought back to life...
Dihidupkan kembali... untuk menghidupkan kembali!
I was brought back to life, to give life!
Kesempatan kedua...
A second chance...
Kembalinya peluang...
Another shot...
Kelahiran kembali...
Rebirth...
Semuanya masuk akal!
It makes sense now!
Tapi, kenapa kekuatanku baru muncul sekarang ya?
But, I wonder why these powers only manifested now though...?
Ah! Jangan-jangan...
Oh! Could it be...
Karena sebelumnya aku pernah memakai kekuatan ini...
That I used my own powers on... Myself?
Kekuatan ini aku pakai untuk bangkit kembali...
I used these powers to come back to life...
Sehingga butuh waktu untuk energinya kembali.
And it took many of its energies... for the power to return.
Masuk akal sih.
That would explain a lot.
Ternyata benar kata chat, aku bisa membuat orang jadi zombie!
I guess chat was right, I could turn people into zombies...
Walaupun dalam makna yang berbeda.
Just, in a different light...
Rasanya seperti bisa menghidupkan apapun!
I feel like I could reanimate anything!
Tapi, aku tahu apa yang ingin aku hidupkan kembali terlebih dahulu.
Well, I know what I'll be reviving first!
Para harapan.
Hope.
Mimpi.
Dreams.
Keinginan.
Wishes.
Motivasi!
Motivation...
Akan aku buat semua bunga layu itu... mati suri!
I'll make those wilted flowers undead!
アンデッドアリスへ
To Undead Alice
思うようにいけないなら私を捨て
If things don't go as you wish, then throw me away
君は生きて
And you, live on
狂ってんだ君の残響は
It's crazy, your reverberation
僕じゃなくたって聴こえるのに
Can be heard even if it's not by me
自傷案を募るたびに
Every time self-harming ideas gather
幸せ吸って毒を吐いて
I inhale happiness and exhale poison
幻想ジャンキー 二人だけが
Illusion junkie, just the two of us
正常なんて気持ちいいじゃんか
Being normal feels good, doesn't it?
会いたいも貸した病が
Even "wanting to meet" is a lent illness
愛なくて惚れた不幸が
Being in love without love is a misfortune
仲良くなっちゃってヤバそうらや
Getting along and it looks dangerous
ドキドキドキになっちゃって
It's becoming a heart-pounding mess
僕が君を殺す前に
Before I kill you
死んでくれ
Please die
ずるしていいよ
It's okay to cheat
ずるくていいよ
It's okay to be sly
壊していいよ
It's okay to break it
怖くていいよ
It's okay to be afraid
卑怯な愛はここに埋めよう
Let's bury this cowardly love here
忘れるんだこんなのもうやめよう
Forget it, let's stop this already
尖ったほうが嫌っていで
It's better to be sharp and hated
も想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
But it's better to be heavy if you care
もう笑えない僕の アンデッドアリスへ
To my Undead Alice, who can no longer laugh
理想通り僕の夢が
My dreams go exactly as ideal
輝くほど陽は陰ってって
The more they shine, the more the sun sets
犠牲を我慢と呼んで
Calling sacrifice "patience"
汚れた手で鍵を回した
I turned the key with dirty hands
悪いようにしないように
So as not to make it bad
それが詰まり悪い形
That's eventually a bad shape
保存状態 相俟って
Preservation state combined
何度も居た墓を埋めました
I buried the grave I'd been in many times
はだけられた本能が
The bared instinct
正しくなことの希望が
The hope of not being right
仲良くなっちゃってヤバそうらや
Getting along and it looks dangerous
ノロノロノになっちゃって
It's becoming sluggish
僕が僕を殺す前に
Before I kill myself
死んでやる
I'll die
ずるしていいよ
It's okay to cheat
ずるくていいよ
It's okay to be sly
壊していいよ
It's okay to break it
怖くていいよ
It's okay to be afraid
卑怯な愛はここに埋めよう
Let's bury this cowardly love here
忘れるんだこんなのもうやめよう
Forget it, let's stop this already
尖ったほうが嫌っていで
It's better to be sharp and hated
も想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
But it's better to be heavy if you care
もう笑えない僕の アンデッドアリスへ
To my Undead Alice, who can no longer laugh
ずっとこのまま ふたりで夢を見れるって
That we can keep dreaming together just like this
勝手ばかりで 君はどんな顔で笑っていたっけ
Selfishly, I wonder what kind of face you were laughing with
バイバイしたから 元通りなんて幻想だ
Since we said goodbye, getting back to normal is an illusion
バイバイ辛いじゃん 胸を裂いて愛を潰してくれよ
Goodbye is painful, isn't it? Rip my chest open and crush the love
ずるしていいよ
It's okay to cheat
ずるくていいよ
It's okay to be sly
壊していいよ
It's okay to break it
怖くていいよ
It's okay to be afraid
卑怯な愛はここに埋めよう
Let's bury this cowardly love here
忘れるんだこんなのもうやめよう
Forget it, let's stop this already
尖ったほうが嫌っていで
It's better to be sharp and hated
も想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
But it's better to be heavy if you care
もう笑えない僕の アンデッドアリスへ
To my Undead Alice, who can no longer laugh
...なんだっていいじゃんか
...it doesn't matter, does it?
もうやめよう
Let's stop this already.
嫌ったほうが
It's better to hate...
嫌っていい
...and hating is fine.
でも想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
But thinking of you is heavy, so isn't that good?
もう笑えない僕の アンデッドアリス
For me, who can no longer laugh, Undead Alice.
なんだっていい
Anything is fine.
痛いくらいじゃ行脚 止まんないや
Just being in pain won't stop the pilgrimage.
自虐くらいじゃ消えそうもないや
Just self-deprecation won't make me disappear.
ごめんねなんて言えるはずない
There's no way I can say "I'm sorry."
「いつかきっと」なんて笑えるなんて間違いじゃないか
Isn't it a mistake to laugh and say "someday for sure"?
誓うじゃないか
Can't we swear it?
死ねない思いは希望か絶望か
Are the thoughts that won't die hope or despair?
もう笑えない僕の アンデッドアリスへ
To my Undead Alice, who can no longer laugh.
アンデッドアリスへ
To Undead Alice.
ローリンガール
Lyrics, Music: wowaka
Rolling Girl
ロンリーガールはいつまでも 届かない夢見て
Lonely girl is always dreaming of an unreachable dream.
騒がしい頭の中を掻き回して、掻き回して。
Stirring up her noisy head, stirring it up.
「問題ない。」と呟いて、
"No problem," she mutters.
言葉は失われた？
Were the words lost?
もう失敗、もう失敗。間違い探しに終われば、また回るの！
Failure again, failure again. If it ends in a mistake hunt, it spins again!
もう一回、もう一回。「私は今日も転がります。」と、
One more time, one more time. "I will roll again today," she says.
少女は言う 少女は言う 言葉に意味を奏でながら！
The girl says, the girl says, as she plays the meaning into the words!
「もう一回、もう一回。まだですよ、まだまだ先は見えないので。息を止めるの、今。」
"One more time, one more time. Not yet, since the end is still not in sight. Holding my breath, now."
ロンリーガールの成れの果て 届かない色を
The ruin of a lonely girl, unreachable colors...
重なる声と声を混ぜあわせて、混ぜあわせて。
...mixing overlapping voices together, mixing them together.
「問題ない。」と呟いた、
"No problem," she muttered.
言葉は失われた。
The words were lost.
どうなったって良いんだってさ、間違いだって起こしちゃおうと誘う、坂道。
It doesn't matter what happens, let's even make a mistake, she invites, on the slope.
もう一回、もう一回。私をどうか転がしてと
One more time, one more time. Please roll me over.
少女は言う 少女は言う 無口に意味を重ねながら！
The girl says, the girl says, as she silently overlaps the meanings!
「もう一回、もう一回。もう少し、もうすぐ何か見えるだろうと。息を止めるの、今。」
"One more time, one more time. Just a bit more, thinking something will be visible soon. Holding my breath, now."
もう一回、もう一回。「私は今日も転がります。」と、
One more time, one more time. "I will roll again today," she says.
少女は言う 少女は言う 言葉に笑みを奏でながら！
The girl says, the girl says, as she plays a smile into the words!
「もう一回、もういいよ。そろそろ君も疲れたろう、ね。息をやめるの、今。」
"One more time, it's enough already. You must be tired by now, right. Stopping my breath, now."
蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Lyrics, Music: DATEKEN
Mitsuzuki Un Deux Trois
誰も居なくなった 二人だけの街に
In the town where no one is left, only the two of us...
機械仕掛けの時計が 夜の訪れ知らせる
...a clockwork timepiece announces the arrival of night.
夕闇が空を ワインに色染めて
The twilight dyes the sky in the color of wine...
...へと誘う 不慣れな二人は
...inviting. The unaccustomed pair
舞台へと誘う
are invited to the stage.
Chasse 'n' Whisk and Natural turn
あなたに魔法をあげる
I'll cast a spell on you.
Throwaway and Oversway
その名前はHoney 蜜月
The name is Honey Honeymoon.
蜜月 アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois.
互いの指を絡めて
With our fingers entwined,
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の夢を奏でる
playing our dreams.
One, two, three! One, two, three! One, two, three!
Chasse 'n' Whisk and Natural turn
あなたに魔法をあげる
I'll cast a spell on you.
Throwaway and Oversway
魅惑の蜜 Honey 蜜月
Enchanting nectar Honey Honeymoon.
蜜月 アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois.
その唇を重ねて
Pressing those lips together,
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の愛を奏でる
playing our love.
月明かり 夜路を 黄金色に照らして
Moonlight illuminates the night path in golden color.
幼い二人は 爪先立ちから踊る
The young pair dances on tiptoe.
蜜月 アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois.
互いの指を絡めて
With our fingers entwined,
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の夢を奏でる
playing our dreams.
Shappadappa 蜜月 アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Shappadappa Honeymoon Un Deux Trois.
その唇を重ねて
Pressing those lips together,
Singin' Swingin' Sweetest Song
二人の愛を奏でる
playing our love.
Huah... Banyak sekali mimpi yang bermekar kembali! Syukurlah!
Ah! I revived so many dreams! I'm so glad!
Tapi, masih ada satu mimpi yang ingin aku bangkitkan kembali.
Though one dream hasn't been revived yet...
Yaitu...
Yes! That is...
Tampil kembali bersama kesayanganku!
To relive my best moments with my beloved!
寂しくて切ない一人の夜には
On a lonely and painful night all alone,
消えたい言葉を探して
I look for words I want to disappear.
秘密のドアを抜けてきて Here we go, Oh yeah!
Come through the secret door. Here we go, Oh yeah!
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
shake it!
目の前の扉を開ければそう
If you open the door in front of you, yes,
終わりのない夜への始まりだ
it's the beginning of a never-ending night.
劇場のフロアの影から
From the shadows of the theater floor,
４次元の旅が始まるよ
a four-dimensional journey begins.
遊星群の箱舟に乗ってさ
Get on the Ark of the Galactic Nebula,
時空を越えへと進んで行くのさ
and proceed beyond space and time.
天気予報はあてにならないから
Since the weather forecast is unreliable,
気の向くまま All right! All right!
just as you please, All right! All right!
Today is the night! Bucky bucky funky night!
You and I together funky funky funky night!
You and I funky night!
Oh...
あげてけ！ Dance Dance 君の瞳から
Dance on! Dance Dance, from your eyes
輝きだす 流れ星が
A shooting star begins to shine
秘密の扉を抜けてきて Here we go
Come through the secret door, here we go
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Shake Shake 今夜は止まらない
Shake Shake, tonight is unstoppable
だから今は wow 夢の中
So now, wow, in the middle of a dream
ミラーボールが回り回る Hurry up
The mirror ball spins round and round, hurry up
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Dance Dance 君の瞳から
Dance Dance, from your eyes
Shake Shake 今夜は止まらない
Shake Shake, tonight is unstoppable
止まらない
Won't stop
あげてけ！ Dance Dance 君の瞳から
Dance on! Dance Dance, from your eyes
輝きだす 流れ星が
A shooting star begins to shine
秘密の扉を抜けてきて Here we go
Come through the secret door, here we go
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Shake Shake 今夜は止まらない
Shake Shake, tonight is unstoppable
だから今は wow 夢の中
So now, wow, in the middle of a dream
ミラーボールが回り回る Hurry up
The mirror ball spins round and round, hurry up
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
寂しくて 切ない一人の夜には
On lonely and painful nights alone
消えない言葉をさがして
Looking for words that won't fade away
秘密の扉を抜けてきて Here we go
Come through the secret door, here we go
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Shake Shake 今夜は止まらない
Shake Shake, tonight is unstoppable
だから今は wow 夢の中
So now, wow, in the middle of a dream
ミラーボールが回り回る Hurry up
The mirror ball spins round and round, hurry up
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah!
Talents
Kureiji Ollie / Ayunda Risu / Moona Hoshinova / Airani Iofifteen / Anya Melfissa / Pavolia Reine / Vestia Zeta / Kaela Kovalskia / Kobo Kanaeru / Hanasaki Miyabi
Instrumentals and mixing: Tyas Pratama Mulyawan
Tuning: Anislanang
Lyrics Overlay: Wyuusan
Animation
Teadium
driving me
Kureiji Ollie's NEW ORIGINAL SONG!!
Digital and MV release soon!!
Halo semuanya! Yahoo!
Hello everyone! Yahoo!
Dengan Ollie di sini. It's me, Ollie. Ollie dayo!
Ollie's here. It's me, Ollie. It's Ollie!
Terima kasih banyak ya sudah nonton 3D Live Ollie.
Thank you so much for watching my 3D Live.
Thank you so much for taking the time to watch my 3D Live.
REBIRTHの3Dライブを見てくれて、本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much for watching the REBIRTH 3D live.
Selain pengumuman lagu original Ollie yang tadi,
Besides the announcement for my original song earlier,
masih ada beberapa pengumuman yang seru lagi lho!
there are still a few more exciting announcements!
Aside from the original song that I'll be releasing,
there are still a few more exciting announcements that I want to make.
えっと、新曲とまだちょっと告知があります。
Um, I have a new song and a few more announcements.
はい！グッズ告知があります！
Yes! I have merch announcements!
We have merch announcements! Ada pengumuman untuk merch!
We have merch announcements! There's an announcement for merch!
Mari kita lihat goods-nya bareng-bareng ya!
Let's take a look at the merch together!
Let's take a look at them together!
じゃ、早速グッズ見てみましょうか！
So, let's take a look at the merch right away!
はい！これだ！Birthday Merch Set-nya!
Yes! This is it! The Birthday Merch Set!
Here is the Birthday Merch Set!
誕生日記念グッズセットになります！いっぱいあるでしょ？
It's the birthday commemorative merch set! There's a lot, right?
Cantik banget kan ya? Aren't they just beautiful?
They're very beautiful, right? Aren't they just beautiful?
本当に素敵でしょ？
They're really wonderful, right?
Seperti yang kalian lihat, kalau kalian membeli satu set,
As you can see, if you buy a full set,
kalian bakal dapat bonus lho!
you'll get a bonus!
And as you guys can see, with every full set purchase,
you'll get an additional bonus!
そして、フルセット購入特典もありますよ！
And there is also a full set purchase bonus!
見ての通り、フルセット購入することに...
As you can see, by purchasing the full set...
...さらにボーナスがついてくるよ！はーい！
...you'll get an additional bonus! Yay!
Kalau kalian membeli full set-nya,
If you buy the full set,
nanti kalian akan mendapatkan postcard yang berisi tanda tangan dan tulisan tangan Ollie!
you'll get a postcard with Ollie's signature and handwritten message!
That's right! If you guys decide to get the full whole set,
then you guys will get a bonus postcard with my signature and a handwritten message!
そうですよ！フルセットお買い上げの方には、
That's right! For those who purchase the full set,
オリーの手書きのメッセージとサインが入った特典ポストカードを差し上げます！
I will give you a bonus postcard with Ollie's handwritten message and signature!
Gambarnya sendiri dibuat oleh Nanahami-sensei!
The illustration itself was made by Nanahami-sensei!
For the drawing itself, it was illustrated by the one and only Nanahami-sensei!
この絵そのものは、えっと、生ハミ先生が描いてくれました！ありがとうございます！
This drawing itself was drawn by Nanahami-sensei! Thank you very much!
Dan yang namanya postcard bertanda tangan, berarti ini siapa cepat dia dapat, dong!
And since it's an autographed postcard, it means first come, first served!
So, what are you waiting for? Go buy the set and get your hands on this baby ASAP!
だからね、このポストカードをできるだけ早く手に入れてください！
So, please get your hands on this postcard as soon as possible!
Emang kalau beli full set cuma ini aja dapetnya, Ollie?
"Is this all we get if we buy the full set, Ollie?"
Ya tentu tidak! Ollie menyiapkan goods-goods menarik yang lainnya lho untuk birthday set Ollie.
Of course not! Ollie has prepared other interesting goods for Ollie's birthday set.
And of course, this is only the bonus and not the only thing that you'll be getting from the set.
I still have other goods to offer you guys!
もちろん、これはただのボーナスだよ！
Of course, this is just the bonus!
まだまだ紹介したいアメイジングなグッズがあるよ！はーい！
There are still more amazing goods I want to introduce! Yay!
REBIRTH Acrylic Diorama Stand! Yay!
Wah, keren banget gak sih? Gambar yang dari postcard tadi jadi kayak timbul kayak gini!
Wow, isn't it so cool? The drawing from the postcard looks like it's popping out like this!
Isn't it just so cool? The illustration just pops right at you!
本当に素敵ですね！ジオラマのエフェクトはめちゃくちゃ美しいです！
It's truly wonderful! The diorama effect is incredibly beautiful!
Dan gambar ini pokoknya cakep banget. Cuma menurut Ollie sih ya, lebih cakep lagi versi nyatanya, guys! Jadi tolong dibeli ya!
And this drawing is just beautiful. But in Ollie's opinion, the real version is even better! So please buy it!
It's a lot cooler in real life, so I suggest you guys to buy it and see for yourself!
えっと、リアルではもっとかっこいいので、ぜひ買って自分の目で確かめてほしいです！
Um, it looks even cooler in real life, so I want you to buy it and see for yourself!
では、次のグッズ！はーい！
Now, the next item! Yay!
REBIRTH Plushie Keychain!
Ah, gemoy banget! Pengen kubawa pulang!
Ah, so cute! I want to take it home!
It's so cute that I just want to keep it all to myself!
可愛すぎて、とろけちゃうよ！もう！
It's so cute, I'm melting! Jeez!
Dengan ini kalian bisa ngajak Ollie jalan-jalan pake kostum REBIRTH kapanpun!
With this, you can take Ollie on a walk in the REBIRTH costume anytime!
With this, you can take me out with the REBIRTH costume wherever and whenever you want!
これさえあれば、いつでもどこでも好きな時にREBIRTHオリーを連れて歩くことができます！わーい！
With this, you can take REBIRTH Ollie along anytime, anywhere you want! Yay!
はーい！
Yay!
Terus kalian juga bisa matching sama REBIRTH Ollie dengan gelang REBIRTH Bracelet!
And you can also match with REBIRTH Ollie with the REBIRTH Bracelet!
You guys can also match yourselves with REBIRTH Ollie with the REBIRTH Bracelet!
REBIRTHオリーとREBIRTHブレスレットとお揃いにすることもできる！
You can also match with REBIRTH Ollie and the REBIRTH Bracelet!
Pokoknya totalitas banget deh! Very cute, very mindful, very demure!
Basically, it's the total package! Very cute, very mindful, very demure!
シックで、かっこいいで、美しいです！はーい！
It's chic, cool, and beautiful! Yay!
Tapi bukan itu saja teman-teman! Ada juga voice pack-nya!
But that's not all, friends! There are also voice packs!
Not only that, but we also have voice packs!
それだけではない！ボイスパックもあるよ！
Not only that! There are also voice packs!
Ada yang Bahasa Indonesia...
There is the Indonesian version...
There's an English version...
そして、日本語までもあるよ！ぜひぜひ聞いてくださいね！
And there's even a Japanese version! Please listen to them!
はーい！
Yay!
Tolong dibeli ya teman-teman!
Please buy them, friends!
Please, please, please buy them!
グッズをお買い求めくださいね！
Please purchase the goods!
Dan kalau kalian beli set-set ini, kalian akan mendapatkan kejutan bonus satu lagi!
And if you buy these sets, you will get another surprise bonus!
And I mentioned the bonus card at the start but actually there will be another bonus that comes along with this birthday merch.
そしてね、実はフルセット買ったらもう一つボーナスがあるよ！
And actually, if you buy the full set, there's one more bonus!
ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEのクレイジー・オリーカード！わーい！
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME Kureiji Ollie card! Yay!
Jadi Ollie REBIRTH juga akan muncul di hololive official card game lho!
So REBIRTH Ollie will also appear in the hololive official card game!
So REBIRTH Ollie will also be making an appearance in hololive official card game!
そう、REBIRTHオリーはhololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEにも登場するよ！
Yes, REBIRTH Ollie will also appear in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME!
Tiap pembelian satu merch set nanti akan disertai dengan satu lembar bonus card!
Each purchase of one merch set will come with one bonus card!
For every merch set purchased, it will also come with a bonus card that can be used in the hololive official card game!
えっと、グッズセット特典として、hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使用できるカードが１枚同梱！
Um, as a goods set bonus, one card that can be used in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME is included!
Ini hanya tersedia bagi yang membeli lewat hololive production official shop, dan kartunya hanya akan tersedia dalam Bahasa Jepang ya guys!
This is only available for those who buy through the hololive production official shop, and the card will only be available in Japanese, guys!
This is only available for those of you guys who purchase through the hololive production official shop, and the card will only be available in Japanese!
あと、こちらは、ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで
And this is available at the hololive production official shop
ご購入いただいた方限定で、
exclusively for those who purchase the set,
えーと、カードは日本語のみとなります。
um, the card will be in Japanese only.
Jadi, tunggu apa lagi? Ayo buruan dibeli!
So, what are you waiting for? Go buy it now!
Untuk detailnya silakan dicek di website penjualannya ya!
For details, please check the sales website!
So, what are you waiting for? Get your hands on these goods right now...
...through the links in the description below.
Details will also be listed in the websites, so please check that out too.
ね、えーと、ほらほらお兄さん、お姉さんたち、
Hey, um, look, look, brothers and sisters!
下記のリンクから今すぐこれらの商品を手に入れよう！
Get these products right now from the link below!
詳細は各ウェブサイトにも掲載されているので、ぜひチェックしてみてください。
Details are listed on each website, so please be sure to check them out.
Sekian itu saja ya teman-teman. Terima kasih banyak telah menyaksikan REBIRTH 3D Live Ollie!
That's all from me, friends. Thank you so much for watching Ollie's REBIRTH 3D Live!
And that's all from me. Thank you so much for watching my REBIRTH 3D live.
えーと、オリの3Dライブを見てくれて、本当に心からありがとうございました！
Um, thank you so much from the bottom of my heart for watching Ollie's 3D live!
これからもオリを応援してね！
Please continue to support Ollie!
おつクレイジー！バイバーイ！
Otsu-Crazy! Bye-bye!